let's go over how you can save an object
让我们来看看如何保存对象
with a transparent background using
具有透明背景，使用
inkscape the first thing you'll want to
Inkscape是你想要做的第一件事
do is create a selection around the
要做的就是围绕
object you'd like to save so I'm going
您要保存的对象，因此我要
to click on this grouping of objects
要单击此对象分组，请执行以下操作
right here and for this demonstration
就在这里，为了这个演示
I'm going to save this icon with a
我要用一个
transparent background once you have
一旦你有透明的背景
your selection enabled open up the
您的选择已启用，打开
export menu by going to file and
通过转到文件和导出菜单
selecting
选择
export from the export menu make sure
从导出菜单中导出请确保
you have the selection tab enabled and
您已启用选择选项卡，并且
come down here to this little thumbnail
到这里来看看这个小小的缩略图
preview that shows you a preview of
向您显示预览的预览
what's going to be saved
什么将会被拯救
now if you just want your selection to
现在，如果你只是想让你的选择
be saved with a transparent background
以透明背景保存
and nothing else make sure to click this
没有其他东西可以确保点击此按钮
button right here that says export
按钮就在这里，上面写着输出
selection only and once you do that
仅限选择，一旦您这样做了
you'll notice the background there
你会注意到那里的背景
changes to a checkerboard pattern
对棋盘图案的更改
indicating transparency if you don't
如果您不这样做，则表示透明度
have this option selected it's going to
选择此选项后，它将
export everything within the bounding
导出边界内的所有内容
box of the selection here which is what
框中的选择在这里是什么
I don't want so I'm going to enable that
我不想要，所以我要启用它
again and now to save this I'm going to
一次又一次，为了挽救这一切，我要
click on this folder icon down here to
单击此处下面的文件夹图标以
choose a location on my hard drive to
在我的硬盘上选择一个位置
save it to before you do that though
不过，在执行此操作之前，请将其保存到
come over here to this drop down and
到这里来，到这里来，然后
make sure you choose portable Network
确保您选择便携网络
graphic or PNG PNG is the file format
文件格式为GRAPH或PNG PNG
that supports transparency once you do
一旦你这样做了，它就会支持透明度
that click on the folder choose a name
点击文件夹选择一个名称
for your document I'm just going to name
对于你的文件，我只想命名
this icon and then I'm going to click
这个图标，然后我要点击
save and if you navigate over to the
保存，如果您导航到
section on your hard drive where you
在您的硬盘上，您可以在
have saved your file you should see your
已保存您的文件，您应该会看到
PNG has been saved there with a
PNG已保存在那里，并带有
transparent background as you can see
如您所见的透明背景
there and that is how you can export a
这就是您如何导出
PNG with a transparent background using
具有透明背景的PNG使用
inkscape join the logos by Nick mailing
Inkscape加入徽标，尼克·梅林
listing get over 200 free design
挂牌获得超过200个免费设计
templates including logos avatars
包括徽标化身的模板
textures infographics and more as a
纹理信息图形等作为
member you'll receive news updates and
会员您将收到新闻更新，
tips about your favorite design apps
有关您最喜欢的设计应用程序的提示
just use the link below to subscribe for
只需使用下面的链接订阅
free and download your templates as
免费并下载您的模板作为
always thanks for watching
始终感谢观看